MAX MORRIS

(803) 378-4290

mjmorris2424@gmail.com 572 John Ross Pkwy Ste 107 #125 Rock Hill, SC

Profile

Dedicated Registered Nurse (RN) with interest in emergency, medical-surgical and psychiatric/mental health nursing. Developed strong physical and psychiatric assessment-evaluation and treatment-planning skills through recent supervised clinical/work experiences.

Reliable, ethical healthcare provider with ability to stay calm and intervene during crises, to facilitate groups and educational seminars, and to collaborate on multidisciplinary teams. Proven ability to build positive relationships with patients, family members, physicians and other medical professionals.

Key Accomplishments:

BLS (Basic Life Support) CPI (Crisis Prevention Institute)

Experience

Cross Country Nursing Agency 7/2020 - Current

(Palmetto Lowcountry Behavioral Health Charleston, SC) 4/2021 - Current

Performed behavioral health assessments.

Administered medications.

Lead group therapy meetings.

Performed admissions/discharges and planned outpatient/follow-up care.

Cross Country Nursing Agency 7/2020 - Current

(Department of Juvenile Justice) 7/2020 - 4/2021

Performed Physical Exams on incoming Juveniles.

Administered Medications.

Coordinated Vaccinations for Incoming Juveniles.

Coordinated Provider Appointments.

Assisted with Juvenile Transfers and Releases.

Behavioral Health Emergency Department Novant Health Charlotte, NC 07/2019 - 10/2020

Performed behavioral health assessments.

Administered medications.

Lead Code Team for Violent patients.

Performed admissions/discharges and planned outpatient/follow-up care.

Healthtrust (Parallon) Workforce Solutions HCA 03/2016 - 10/2020

(Reston Hospital Center ER/Dominion Psychiatric Hospital) (Reston)

Performed emergency nursing care to patients of all ages.

Led code situations including but not limited to cardiac arrest, respiratory distress, massive trauma, and neurological/psychiatric illnesses.

Performed administrative duties such as hospital admissions and discharges/follow up appointments.

(Dominion Psychiatric Hospital)

Performed behavioral health assessments.

Administered medications.

Lead group therapy meetings.

Performed admissions/discharges and planned outpatient/follow-up care.

Emergency Department Dorn VA Medical Center 10-2014 - 03-2016 Columbia, SC

Performed emergency nursing care to patients of all ages.

Led code situations including but not limited to cardiac arrest, respiratory distress, massive trauma, and neurological/psychiatric illnesses.

Performed administrative duties such as hospital admissions and discharges/follow up appointments.

Providence Hospital

07/2012 - 03/2016 Columbia, SC Emergency Department

Performed emergency nursing care to patients of all ages.

Led code situations including but not limited to cardiac arrest, respiratory distress, massive trauma, and neurological/psychiatric illnesses.

Performed administrative duties such as hospital admissions and discharges/follow up appointments.

Providence Hospital (Lab)

11/2008 - 07/2012 Columbia, SC Lab Tech

MLT (ASCP) generalist in the four major areas of the laboratory including Blood bank, Hematology, Microbiology, and Chemistry.

Performed phlebotomy in the outpatient clinic.

Providence Hospital

(3 Heart) 12/2011 - 07/2012

Nurse Tech

Performed patient Vital Signs, Intake and Output, and Blood Sugars.

Performed patient hygiene, linen changes, and managed snack distribution in patients with special diets

United States Air Force Reserve 03-2008 – Current Charleston, SC Tech Sgt.

Health Service Management Apprentice – Coordinates patient's annual health assessment and flight physicals.

Drug Demand Reduction - Prepare the list and coordinate random base wide drug screening.

Laboratory – Draw patients' blood and prepare for shipping to testing facility.

Education

08/2010 – 05/2012 Orangeburg-Calhoun Technical College, Orangeburg, SC Associate Degree in Nursing

Senior Practicum: Three semesters that entailed time on a psychiatric unit, Bryan's Psychiatric Hospital (BPH) and in the medical-surgical setting at the Regional Medical Center (RMC). Worked intensively with patients to promote their interest and participation in reality, identify problems and solutions, and enhance their coping skills. Provided a safe and therapeutic environment for psychiatric patients. Also provided safe, patient-centered care that focused on detailed assessments to optimize healing in the medical-surgical setting.

Nursing Curriculum Highlights: Family and Community Nursing, Healthcare Delivery Models, Physical Health Assessment, Clinical and Chemical Therapeutics, Pharmacology, Psychosocial Pathology, Human Anatomy and Physiology, Statistics, Nursing Research

8/2016 – 5/2018 Community College of the Air Force Charleston, SC Associates Degree in Health Service Management

08/2006 – 05/2008 Orangeburg- Calhoun Technical College Orangeburg, SC Associates Degree in Applied Science (Medical Laboratory Technician)

References

Available upon request